Dizzy,dizzy,can you fill me
眩晕、困顿能否填补我的残缺？
Up 'til I'm myself
直到寻回自我
Body's scattered 'cross the floor
摊开四肢横躺在地
Could have sworn I've been here before
我发誓此刻似曾相识
Oh, you still here?
噢，你还在这？
Hoping for a banger? Wait another year
想要一点节奏？来年气氛暴走
I'm preoccupied with my career
社畜只想上工禀奏
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
Break me, take me, make me, hate me
击垮我、带走我、成就我、憎恨我
I'm already there, yeah
此刻这里正是我，耶
And the icing on top
顶端的糖霜
Was the glitter I dropped
是我挥洒的光芒
And the avalanche came to drown me bitter
雪崩将我埋葬
Keep me hollow 'til tomorrow
空虚直到天亮
Won't I bother you with all my with all my
我不会扰你心烦，全心全意
Dress how you wanna, feel how you wanna
穿上你的偏爱，感受你的自在
Won't I bother you with all my tears?
我的眼泪是否惹你无奈？
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
I want that that
我想要那……
Blue sugar high
蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态
I want that that blue sugar high
我想要那蓝色砂糖给予我灵感
To cut me up
剖析我
Paint my insides
描绘我内心姿态